export const data = [
    {
        id: 11,
        question: 'brain bridge least through whom wood whose rate hearing.',
        answer:'tiny writer die mountain cause common plates stuck honor stay broken heavy area strength.'
    },
    {
        id: 85,
        question: 'positive tube nothing came rays fifth building physical club softly.',
        answer:'daily pipe fine rapidly pour mental closer complete inside arm pitch gently halfway around baby reader.'
    },
    {
        id: 47,
        question: 'save mostly weak steep four military rain aloud each busy nation discu.wing',
        answer:'minerals wish bite night heard station land pencil business another separate mud soun.'
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: 'shot lovely mind lose total visitor green sat cow .',
        answer:'ability list think offer judge warn beauty together club warm handsome death communit.'
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'tea specific agree kept clothes relationship rubbed fed however bl.t',
        answer:'previous action chemical sheep community dawn character seat customs eye other rather characteristic yest.'
    },
    {
        id: 62,
        question: 'pipe string explore goose after offer tin jump monkey mail fact exp.nt',
        answer:'rocky sudden sum might color child pet rubbed crowd contrast tiny degree diffic.'
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'outer organized active north fat front per numeral accept .',
        answer:'threw curious fear find entire creature cotton castle parts limited coming requ.'
    },
    {
        id: 33,
        question: 'funny slightly high improve atom day television tell .',
        answer:'alike satisfied circus closer fall sentence army breathe running future pig have least trouble dre.'
    },
    {
        id: 58,
        question: 'pressure needs base guess noted led city figure birds toward vessel.dly slowly',
        answer:'nodded paid due electric object likely habit indeed dog sets wing stop chain cl.'
    },
    {
        id: 82,
        question: 'present bar author eat rocky something very arrange run flat conve.',
        answer:'learn society pole gravity while sell bottle win among farmer darkness stick bear se.'
    },
    {
        id: 85,
        question: 'turn fast start ants composed gas late eaten cost leave sens.',
        answer:'helpful throughout jungle zero six straight farther worried job classroom support soon correctly proces.'
    },
]